{
    "subject": "resource/Deborah_Jeane_Palfrey",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Deborah Jeane Palfrey",
    "human_readable": "The name of Deborah Jeane Palfrey is Deborah Jeane Palfrey.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9838131666183472,
            "question": "What is the full name of Deborah Jeane Palfrey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9580134153366089,
            "question": "What is the significance of the name 'Deborah Jeane Palfrey'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9564138054847717,
            "question": "Are there any other names associated with Deborah Jeane Palfrey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9380427002906799,
            "question": "Is Deborah Jeane Palfrey a real person?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.905749499797821,
            "question": "What is known about Deborah Jeane Palfrey's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8568270802497864,
            "question": "Is there any public information available about Deborah Jeane Palfrey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.851019024848938,
            "question": "How would you describe Deborah Jeane Palfrey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.850745439529419,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Deborah Jeane Palfrey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8495888710021973,
            "question": "Where can I find more details about Deborah Jeane Palfrey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7047181725502014,
            "question": "What are some common misconceptions about Deborah Jeane Palfrey?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Deborah Jeane Palfrey is Deborah Jeane Palfrey.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2227_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can I find more details about Deborah Jeane Palfrey?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2227_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Deborah Jeane Palfrey?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2227_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you describe Deborah Jeane Palfrey?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2227_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2227_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2227_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2227_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2227_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2227_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2227_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2227_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2227_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2227_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2227_71.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate!  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The triple to be evaluated is:\n\n\"Deborah Jeane Palfrey, the D.C. Madam, was a woman.\"\n\nHere's the evaluation in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents consistently refer to the individual as \"Deborah Jeane Palfrey\" throughout, confirming that her full name is indeed \"Deborah Jeane Palfrey.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}